http://www.wetplanetwhitewater.com/privacy-policy/

QUESTIONS? info@wetplanetwhitewater.com 877.390.9445
Reserve NowRaftingDay TripsMulti-Day TripsGroups & PackagesPlanning a TripClass SystemKayakingKayak CoursesAdvanced ClinicsMulti-Day Kayak TripsYouth ProgramsKayaking Skill LevelsPro TrainingRiver Rescue CoursesTechnical
Rope RescueACA Kayak Instructor CourseWilderness Medicine CoursesRaft Guide SchoolStoreWhy Wet PlanetAbout UsGuest TestimonialsFrequent FloatersOur StaffOur PlanetWet Planet Café + GrillAnnual White Salmon River FestBlogInfoContact UsLocation & DirectionsFAQGift CertificatesRegional LinksLodging PartnersPoliciesEmployment OpportunitiesSitemapReserve NowQUESTIONS? info@wetplanetwhitewater.com 877.390.9445RaftingDay TripsMulti-Day TripsGroups & PackagesPlanning a TripClass SystemKayakingKayak CoursesAdvanced ClinicsMulti-Day Kayak TripsYouth ProgramsKayaking Skill LevelsPro TrainingRiver Rescue CoursesTechnical
Rope RescueACA Kayak Instructor CourseWilderness Medicine CoursesRaft Guide SchoolStoreWhy Wet PlanetAbout UsGuest TestimonialsFrequent FloatersOur StaffOur PlanetWet Planet Café + GrillAnnual White Salmon River FestBlogInfoContact UsLocation & DirectionsFAQGift CertificatesRegional LinksLodging PartnersPoliciesEmployment OpportunitiesSitemapReserve NowPrivacy PolicyPersonal Information We CollectIn order to process requests for information or to create a reservation, we will collect personal information from you. The information may include your name, mailing or billing address, email address, phone number, or other information needed for a specific trip (i.e. date of birth, height and weight). We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information to us on a voluntary basis. We also keep track of the trips you have participated in with Wet Planet.Wet Planet Rafting and Kayaking will use the information you provide to us in order to: process your request, bill you for your reservation, provide you with documents and information needed for your trip, make sure any personalized equipment or services are available for your trip, communicate with you regarding your trip, and to communicate with you in the future about products and services that may be of interest to you.Do we share your information with other companies or any other third party?No.Do we sell your information to anyone?No.This Website Uses Google AnalyticsWe use “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy.Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site or opt-out of Google Analytics by disabling cookies on your web browser.This Website Uses Google AdWordsThis website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an inquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Wet Planet website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.Why did you receive an email from us?Our email marketing is permission based. If you receive an email from Wet Planet, our records indicate that you have expressly shared your email address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or you have registered or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.How can you stop receiving email from us?Each email sent by Wet Planet has an automated method to unsubscribe from our email list in the form of a link at the bottom of the email. You can also request to no longer receive emails by sending us a quick message at info@wetplanetwhitewater.com.Using Our WebsiteYou are using our website at your own risk. Children under the age of 13 must be accompanied by an adult if logging into our trip registration or online reservation system.Who should you talk to if you have a question about your privacy?Call us at 800.306.1673 and we will be more than happy to discuss concerns you may have about your privacy. Get Our NewsletterEmail*
Leave this field empty if you're human: ©2019 Wet Planet Rafting, Inc.  |  Privacy  |  Policies  |  Sitemap  |  Contact
Our Annual Black Friday Special is almost here!Up to 50% off on select rafting trips and kayak courses. Our November E-newsletter is the only place to find the discount code. Don't miss out - sign up for the newsletter now. Email*
Leave this field empty if you're human:
